# SERGIO ARCHILA (26 years)

Objective: Junior Front-End Developer

**+57 3505007573** 

□ archilargosergio@gmail.com

**O**github.com/Archilargosergio

in linkedin.com/in/sergio



Empirical and self-taught Font-End Developer with highly academic experience in JS language with enough knowledge in OOP and pattern design.

Currently interested in belonging to a collaborating team that wants to grow professionally and personally in programming stuffs.

## **Skills:**

JavaScript, ReactJS HTML5, CSS3, SASS, NPM, XML, JSX, OOP, Design Patterns/Design Principals, Git, GitHub, Atom, VSCode, (Learning Node.JS)

## Portfolio:

https://fancy-daifuku-45d1f2.netlify.app

## **Professional experience:**

**2022 – Now:** Freelancer Front-End Developer with JavaScript and ReactJS.

**2022 – Now:** Administrative office assistant – IT Business in EPAM Anywhere – Remote work.

**2021:** Trilingual agent (English, French, Spanish) in Teleperformance – Colombia, Remote work.

GitHub Professional Course, Basic
JavaScript Course, Practical JavaScript
Course, Frontend Developer Course,
Frontend Developer Practical Course, Basic
Course of OOP with JavaScript,
Intermediate Course of OOP in JavaScript.
React.js Practical Course - Platzi
programming development school.

Node.js in AWS Course - RS School.

June 2013- July 2018: Professional diploma in International Business Administration, Universidad Pontificia Bolivariana of Bucaramanga.

### **Hobbies:**

Passionate about play sports, football and also about photography.

## Languages:

English - B2

French – B2

Spanish - Native

#### Formation:

March 2022 - Now: Basic Computing Course, Basic Programming Course, Git and